The weight is over.
South Park: The End of Obesity is a animation, comedy,
tv movie film directed by Trey Parker.
The advent of new weight loss drugs has a huge impact on everyone in South Park.
When Cartman is denied access to the life-changing
medicine, the kids jump into action.
Stan Marsh / Eric Cartman (voice), played by Trey Parker.
Kyle Broflovski / Kenny McCormick / Butters Stotch / Gerald
Broflovski (voice), played by Matt Stone.
Wendy Testaburger / Sharon Marsh / Shelley Marsh / Liane Cartman /
Alexis Testaburger (voice), played by April Stewart.
Sheila Broflovski / Mrs. Tweak / Linda Stotch (voice), played by Mona Marshall.
Laura Tucker / Linda Black (voice), played by Kimberly Brooks.
Additional Voices (voice), played by Jessica Makinson.
"South Park: The End of Obesity" is a 2024 American adult
animated comedy television special episode.
It is the seventh South Park television special,  and
the 328th episode of the series overall.
The special premiered on May 24, 2024, on Paramount+.
The special satirizes celebrities' glamorized usage of semaglutide-based weight loss drugs and Big
Sugar, as well as Lizzo and the inaccessibility of the American health care system.
The film explores themes of obesity, group of
friends, adult animation, weight loss.
The tone is lighthearted.